Site navigation
---------------

ACI Learning privacy statement
==============================

Our Privacy Commitment
----------------------

ACI Learning, a subsidiary of MIS Training Institute Holdings, Inc. (together "we") respects the privacy of every person who visits or registers with our websites ("you"), and are committed to ensuring a safe online experience.

This Privacy Statement outlines the information we may collect about you in relation to your use of our websites and services ("personal data") and how we may use that personal data. It also outlines the methods by which we and tour service providers may monitor your online behavior in order to deliver customized advertisements and marketing materials and other tailored services. This Privacy Statement also tells you how you can verify the accuracy of your personal data and how you can request that we delete or update it.

This Privacy Statement applies to all websites operated by us (as indicated on the relevant website) ("Sites"). For the purpose of this Privacy Statement "Group Company" shall mean MIS Training Institute Holdings, Inc. and any of its subsidiary companies including ACI Learning, MIS Training Institute and LeaderQuest. Please note that the Sites may contain links to external sites and may contain advertisements for, and/or the opportunity for you to purchase products or services from third parties. This privacy statement does not cover the activities of such third parties, and you should consult those third-party sites' privacy policies for information on how your data is used by them.

By accessing and using the Sites you are agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Statement.

Information About Us
--------------------

Our principal business activities are: Organizers of Seminars, Conferences, Training Courses, Certification and Exhibitions for Internal Audit, I.T. Audit, Fraud, Risk, Cybersecurity, IT and Information Security.

MIS Training Institute Holdings, Inc.

Company Address: 6855 S. Havana Suite 420 Centennial, CO80112 United States of America

MIS Training (UK) Limited

Company Address: 85 Great Portland Street London W1W 7LT United Kingdom T: +44 (0)20 3819 0795

Name of the Data Controller

The Data Controller is MIS Training (UK) Limited. MIS Training Institute Holdings, Inc. is subject to the UK Data Protection Act 1998 and is registered in the UK with the Information Commissioner's Office.

### **Personal Information ACI Learning May Collect**

ACI Learning collects personal information online including names, postal and e-mail addresses, phone and facsimile numbers, billing information, and complaint information.

ACI Learning may also collect business information, some of which could constitute personal information, as well as personal information from individuals acting solely in their business capacity.

ACI Learning does not knowingly collect or maintain any personal information from children under the age of 13. In addition, no part of our sites is designed with the purpose of attracting any person under age 13.

ACI Learning, with student consent, may use testimonials provided in student evaluations for promotional purposes but will not use any student personal information in any promotion.

Our primary goal in collecting personal data from you is to give you an enjoyable customized experience whilst allowing us to provide services and features that most likely meet your needs. We collect certain personal data from you, which you give to us when using our Sites and/or registering or subscribing for our products and services. However, we also give you the option to access our Sites' home pages without subscribing or registering or disclosing your personal data. We do not collect information about our Site visitors, registered users or subscribers from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organizations.

Unless you otherwise consent, we will use your personal information only for the purpose for which it is submitted, such as to reply to your emails, handle your complaints, and process billing and business requests related to program participation or follow up marketing notices. We will use such information to provide operational or marketing information and in program record-keeping and when conducting research on industry marketplace practices. Our research may lead to the publication of aggregate demographical data, but will not result in the reporting or publication of any personal information provided to us. At certain points where personal information is collected on our site, there may be a box where you may indicate you would like to be on a mailing list to receive information about other ACI Learning programs and services and about ways to stay connected with ACI Learning. This election box only appears in places where the department collecting personal information maintains such lists. At any time you can add or remove your name from a ACI Learning list by contacting us atsupport@acilearning.com.

### **Types of Personal Data Held and its Use**

We never sell or rent your personal information.

1. Customer Services and Administration: At some Sites, ACI Learning and its MIS Training Institute and LeaderQuest entities collects personal data such as your name, job title, work and/or home address, and telephone number and email address in order to register you for access to certain content and subscriptions. This information may be supplemented with demographic information from your use of our Sites such as your postal area, age, gender, purchasing preferences and interests. At other Sites, ACI Learning may only collect broad demographic information for aggregate use. This information is used to administer and deliver to you the products and/or services you have requested, to operate our Sites efficiently and improve our service to you, and to retain records of our business transactions and communications. By using the Sites and submitting personal information through the registration process you are agreeing that we may collect, hold, process and use your information (including personal information) for the purpose of providing you with the Site services and developing our business, which shall include (without limitation) the purposes described below in paragraphs 2 and 3.
    
2. Monitoring use of our Sites: Where, as part of our Site services, we enable you to post information or materials on our Site, we may access and monitor any information which you upload or input, including in any password-protected sections. We also monitor and/or record the different Sites you visit, and actions taken on those Sites, e.g. content viewed or searched for. If you are a registered user (e.g. a subscriber or taking a trial), when you log on, this places a cookie on your machine. This enables your access to content and services that are not publicly available. Once you are logged on, the actions you take - for example, viewing an article - will be recorded. We may use technology or a service provider to do this for us. This information may be used for one or more of the following purposes:
    
    * to fulfill our obligations to you;
        
    * to improve the efficiency, quality and design of our Sites and services;
        
    * to see which articles, features and services are most often read and used
        
    * to track compliance with our terms and conditions of use, e.g. to ensure that you areacting within the scope of your user license;
        
    * for marketing purposes (subject to your rights to opt-in and opt-out of receiving certain marketing communications) — see paragraph 3 below;
        
    * for advertising purposes, although the information used for these purposes does not identify you personally. Please see paragraph 5 below for more details;
        
    * to protect or comply with our legal rights and obligations; and
        
    * to enable our journalists to contact and interact with you online in connection with any content you may post to our Sites.
        
3. Marketing: Some of your personal data collected under paragraphs 1 and 2 above may be used by us and/or our other group companies and third party service providers to contact you by email, fax, telephone and/or post for sending information or promotional material on our products and/or services and/or those of our other group companies. We give you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving marketing communications and will in certain circumstances need to obtain your consent before sending such communications to you. Further detail can be found on the applicable Site and in each marketing communication contact sent by us, our group companies or service providers. See also "Consents and opt-outs" section below.
    
4. Trading in Personal Data: Some of your personal data may be collected and processed with the intention of selling it to other organizations, but this will not be done unless you have given your consent (separately to this privacy statement).
    
5. Cookies and interest-based advertising
    
    5.1 Cookies: All our Sites use "cookies". A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. ACI Learning uses non-identifying cookies to provide easier site navigation and access to forms. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. They are uniquely assigned to you and can only be read by a Web server in the domain that issued the cookie. As mentioned above, cookies can be used to track behavior on our Sites, building online profiles of our customers. Cookies are either used only during your session ("temporary" or "session state" cookies) or stored on your computer's hard drive ("permanent" cookies). Cookies are integral to the functioning of all the Sites. By using your browser's options to block cookies, you will effectively prohibit effective use of the Sites. If you still wish to control the operation of cookies, then functionality is available through your browser. Generally, you have the options to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is issued or reject all cookies. Please consult your browsers help system for information on how to block cookies. If you are within a corporate environment your systems administrator may have set the preferences for you, in which case their assistance in changing the settings will be required. Our websites are not set up to track, collect, or distribute personal information not entered by visitors. Our site logs do generate certain kinds of non-identifying site usage data, such as the number of hits and visits to our sites. This information is used for internal purposes by technical support staff to provide better services to the public and may also be provided to others, but again, the statistics contain no personal information and cannot be used to gather such information. 5.2 Interest based advertising Interest based advertisements on our site are provided by our advertising partner ([DoubleClick by Google](https://marketingplatform.google.com/about/enterprise/)). Our advertising partner will serve ads that it believes are most likely to be of interest to you, based on certain information about your visit to this and other Sites. This information is collected and used, without reference to other data which could identify you in the real world, in that it does not include your name, street address, email address or telephone number. Please note that, to collect this information for advertising purposes, our advertising provider may need to place a cookie (a small text file) on your computer. You have the right to exercise control over the way we collect and use information about your online activities in this way and you are entitled to opt-out of receiving this type of interest based advertising. For more information about how cookies and this type of interest-based advertising work and how to disable them, you can also visit www.youronlinechoices.co.uk for more information. You can also refer to the privacy policy of DoubleClick by Google if you do not wish to receive interest-based advertising on other sites served by their system. DoubleClick can serve an "opt out" cookie to your device. Please note that the effectiveness of any opt- out for interest-based advertising may be impacted by deleting all cookies on your browser.
    
6. Government-mandated requests ACI Learning may also release personal information under the following circumstances:

* Where release is required by law (for example, a subpoena) or regulation or is requested by a government agency;
    
* Where our records indicate a company may be engaged in fraudulent activity or other deceptive practices that a governmental agency should be made aware of;
    
* To appropriate governmental authorities, where warranted by a company’s failure to participate in the advertising self-regulatory process or respond to an online privacy complaint, or where a company fails to honor the recommendations of the National Advertising Division, Children’s Advertising Review Unit, or National Advertising Review Board;
    
* To appropriate persons, where your communication suggests possible harm to others.

Any other purposes for which ACI Learning & MIS Training Institute Holdings, Inc. wish to use your personal data will be notified to you and your personal data will not be used for any such purpose without obtaining your prior consent.

### Consents and opt-outs

You can give your consent to or opt out of particular uses of your data as indicated above by:

* Indicating in a box at the point on the relevant Site where personal data is collected;
    
* Informing us by email, post or phone; or
    
* Updating your preferences on the applicable Site; or
    
* For behavioral advertising, see link in paragraph 5 above. You can also use your browser's options to control the operation of cookies (please see section 5 above for more details).

Disclosures

Information collected at one Site may be shared between MIS Training Institute Holdings, Inc. and other group companies for the purposes listed above.

Your personal data may also be sold to other companies in the form of lists and directories, but only after permission from you in accordance with the provisions above.

We may also disclose your personal data to other third parties, including, without limitation, professional advisers, or governmental or State institutions or regulatory authorities, where necessary in order to exercise or defend legal rights or where required by law.

We may transfer, sell or assign any of the information described in this policy to third parties as a result of a sale, merger, consolidation, change of control, transfer of assets or reorganization of our business.

Public forums, message boards and blogs

Some of our Sites make message boards, blogs or other facilities for user generated content available and users can participate in these facilities. Any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should always be careful when deciding to disclose your personal information.

Transfers outside the EEA

Services on the Internet are accessible globally so collection and transmission of personal data is not always limited to one country. MIS Training Institute Holdings, Inc. may transfer your personal data, for the purposes listed above, to other group companies, service providers or other third parties which may be located in countries outside the European Economic Area, whose laws may not give the level of protection to personal data as within the UK. This will include transfers to third parties who provide us with email and marketing services. Where we conduct any transfers we will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Statement.

Confidentiality and Security of Your Personal Data

We are committed to keeping the data you provide us secure and will take reasonable precautions to protect your personal data from loss, misuse or alteration. The transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features described above to try to prevent unauthorized access.

We have implemented information security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from:

* unauthorized access
    
* improper use or disclosure
    
* unauthorized modification
    
* unlawful destruction or accidental loss

All our employees, contractors and data processors (i.e. those who process your personal data on our behalf, for the purposes listed above), who have access to, and are associated with the processing of your personal data, are obliged to keep the information confidential and not use it for any other purpose than to carry out the services they are performing for us.

We also give you the option of using a secure transmission method to send us personal data identifiers, such as credit card details and bank account number.

### **How to Access, Update and Erase your Personal Information**

If you wish to know whether we are keeping personal data about you, or if you have an enquiry about our privacy policy or your personal data held by us, in relation to any of the Sites, you can contact the Data Protection Officer via:

**North America**

* Postal mail to this address: Data Protection Officer, ACI Learning, 6855 S Havana St #420, Centennial, CO 80112
    
* Email: support@acilearning.com

**Europe, Middle East, Africa, and Asia Pacific**

* Postal mail to this address: Data Protection Officer, MIS Training (UK) Limited, 85 Great Portland Street, London, W1W 7LT
    
* Email: support@acilearning.com

Upon request, we will provide you with a readable copy of the personal data which we keep about you. We may require proof of your identity and may charge a small fee (not exceeding the statutory maximum fee that can be charged) to cover administration and postage.ACI Learning allows you to challenge the data that we hold about you and, where appropriate in accordance with applicable laws, you may have your personal information:

* erased
    
* rectified or amended
    
* completed

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**

We will occasionally update this Privacy Statement to reflect new legislation or industry practice, group company changes and customer feedback. We encourage you to review this Privacy Statement periodically to be informed of how we are protecting your personal data.

For ACI On Demand Users (subscriptions such as AuditPro):
---------------------------------------------------------

At ACI Learning, we value the privacy and security of your personal information, and are committed to the fair and transparent processing of your information. This Privacy Policy is meant to help you understand what information we collect, why we collect it, and how you can update, manage and delete your information.

### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. We collect only the personal information that we need in order to provide you with the products or services that you order. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Upon written request, we will disclose to you the personal information we hold about you, and will endeavor, to the extent technically feasible, to delete or render inaccessible your personal information. You may also request that we correct or amend such personal information so that any inaccurate or incomplete personal information can be corrected or completed without undue delay. Such requests should be directed to our Director of Privacy, whose contact information is provided below.

We will endeavor to respond to your requests to view, correct or delete your personal information without undue delay, or within approximately one month following verification of your identity. Note that we will undertake a good faith effort to accommodate requests for access to or deletion of personal information. However, these requests may be subject to an evaluation of additional factors, including disproportionate burden or expense, or the risk to the privacy or other rights of others. We may also retain and use your personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, enforce our rights or agreements, and for other lawful business purposes.

The term personal information, as used in this Privacy Policy, includes personal data as defined by the General Data Protection Regulation, personal information or personally identifiable information as defined in various United States data breach notification laws and information that may otherwise be used to identify an individual.

### How do we use your information?

Any of the information we collect from you will only be used to process your order with us and to provide you with informational material relating to other of our products and services that may be of interest to you. However, you have the right to opt out of receiving these additional materials.

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of technical and organizational security measures to maintain the safety, integrity and confidentiality of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database so that it is only accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, who have a role in providing adequate protection to your information.

After a transaction is processed, your private information (credit cards, etc. ) will not be stored on our servers.

### Do we use cookies?

Yes. By using this site and service, you agree to the use of cookies. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits.

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personal information. We may provide certain of your information to trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties provide us assurances that they will provide adequate protection to your information. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect yours, ours or others rights, property, or safety. We do not edit, review or make decisions concerning information you decide to share with others on our site, including, but not limited to, any personal information.

### Links to sites of third parties

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies, which we encourage you to review before inputting any personal information into those sites. However, we have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the My Profile page.

### Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children's Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

### General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)

Because we take the privacy and security of your information very seriously, including our subscribers who reside in the European Union, we are committed to protecting your personal information in accordance with provisions of the GDPR. We are building privacy and security of personal information into our technical and organizational systems and processes related to any personal information we process. We do not sell, exchange or transfer member information for any reason, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the product or service requested. The personal information we collect is limited to that which is necessary to provide the products and services you request, and your information is only kept as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected.

### Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at [https://hub.acilearning.com/terms-and-conditions](https://hub.acilearning.com/terms-and-conditions)

### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

### Changes to this Privacy Statement

We may update, modify or change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent. We always indicate the date the last updates were published. This policy was last modified on November 10, 2021. If the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice.

Contacting Us
-------------

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact customer support ([support@acilearning.com](mailto:support@acilearning.com)) or our Director of Privacy ([dpo@acilearning.com](mailto:dpo@acilearning.com)). You may also contact us using the information below:

ACI Learning  
6855 S Havana St #420  
Centennial, CO 80112

Resources

About ACI Learning

Get Support

Partner With Us

© ACI Learning
